{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "The first, second, and third prizes went to Dora, Esther, and Jennie ___.",
      "a": "partially",
      "b": "equally",
      "c": "differently",
      "d": "respectively",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- respectively: in the same order as the things you have just mentioned",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "The new medicine rescued David from the illness; ___ it might have been desperate.",
      "a": "otherwise",
      "b": "whatever",
      "c": "if",
      "d": "therefore",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- otherwise: used when saying what bad thing will happen if something is not done",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are you going to the concert? \"No, the ticket is ___ expensive for me\"",
      "a": "so much",
      "b": "lots of",
      "c": "far too",
      "d": "very much",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Far too + adjective: a great degree. \n- Ex: far too much/long/busy etc",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ Emily's mother is a charming woman.",
      "a": "For most the part",
      "b": "For the most part",
      "c": "Mostly part",
      "d": "Part for the most",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- For the most/fist/last/best/worst/final part etc",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "This plant is ___ big that it should really be moved outside.",
      "a": "so",
      "b": "too",
      "c": "such",
      "d": "very",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- So that + clause",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Most foreign students don't like American coffee, and ___.",
      "a": "I don't too",
      "b": "either don't I",
      "c": "neither don't I",
      "d": "neither do I",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- ... Don't ...., and neither do + S",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Doctoral students who are preparing to take their qualifying examinations have been studying in the library every night ___ the last three months.",
      "a": "since",
      "b": "for",
      "c": "ago",
      "d": "before",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- for + a period of time (for a moth, a week etc)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Christina is going skiing tomorrow. \"___\"",
      "a": "So am I",
      "b": "So I am",
      "c": "So David is",
      "d": "So does Edmond",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- S + do .... So do + S",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "I haven't turned in papers yet. \" ___\"",
      "a": "So has Kitty",
      "b": "Neither have Kitty",
      "c": "Neither has Kitty",
      "d": "Neither Kitty has",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- S + don't .... Neither + do + S",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "I slipped on the stairs. I think my leg is broken. \"Oh! I ___\"",
      "a": "do not hope so",
      "b": "do not hope",
      "c": "hope not so",
      "d": "hope not",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- I hope not: used to say that you hope something that has been mentioned does not happen or is not true.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}